[
  {
    "Answer": "a",
    "Option-d": "Regression Testing",
    "Question": "Which testing is done by developer?",
    "Option-a": "Unit Testing",
    "Option-b": "Integration Testing",
    "Option-c": "Sanity Testing"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "c",
    "Option-d": "Benchmark Testing",
    "Question": "Which is functional testing?",
    "Option-a": "Load Testing",
    "Option-b": "Security Testing",
    "Option-c": "Gorilla Testing"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "a",
    "Option-d": "Analyzing the cause of failure",
    "Question": "Which of the following is a typical test objective?\n",
    "Option-a": "Preventing defects",
    "Option-b": "Repairing defects",
    "Option-c": "Comparing actual results to expected results"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "d",
    "Option-d": "The defect",
    "Question": "A phone ringing momentarily distracts a programmer, causing the programmer to improperly \nprogram the logic that checks the upper boundary of an input variable. Later, during system \ntesting, a tester notices that this input field accepts invalid input values. The improperly coded logic \nfor the upper boundary check is:\n",
    "Option-a": "The root cause",
    "Option-b": "The failure",
    "Option-c": "The error"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "b",
    "Option-d": "Root cause analysis",
    "Question": "A product owner says that your role as a tester on an Agile team is to catch all the bugs before the \nend of each iteration. Which of the following is a testing principle that could be used to respond to \nthis (false) statement?\n",
    "Option-a": "Defect clustering",
    "Option-b": "Testing shows the presence of defects",
    "Option-c": "Absence of error fallacy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "d",
    "Option-d": "Attention to detail",
    "Question": "Programmers often write and execute unit tests against code which they have written. During this \nself-testing activity, which of the following is a tester mindset that programmers should adopt to \nperform this unit testing effectively?\n",
    "Option-a": "Good communication skills",
    "Option-b": "Code coverage",
    "Option-c": "Evaluating code defects"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "c",
    "Option-d": "Reducing the risk of untestable functionality",
    "Question": "A tester participated in a discussion about proposed database structure. The tester identified a \npotential performance problem related to certain common user searches. This possible problem \nwas explained to the development team. Which of the following is a testing contribution to success \nthat BEST matches this situation?\n",
    "Option-a": "Enabling required tests to be identified at an early stag",
    "Option-b": "Ensuring processes are carried out properly",
    "Option-c": "Reducing the risk of fundamental design defects"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "d",
    "Option-d": " none of the mentioned",
    "Question": "Which of the following is not included in failure costs?\n",
    "Option-a": "rework",
    "Option-b": "repai",
    "Option-c": "failure mode analysis"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "b",
    "Option-d": "documents to be produced by the SQA group",
    "Question": "Which of the following is not a SQA plan for a project?\n",
    "Option-a": "evaluations to be performed",
    "Option-b": "amount of technical work",
    "Option-c": "audits and reviews to be performed"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "a",
    "Option-d": "complaint resolution",
    "Question": "Which of the following is not included in External failure costs?",
    "Option-a": " testing",
    "Option-b": "help line support",
    "Option-c": "warranty work"
  }
]